<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>

    
    <string name="topic_section1">
    <![CDATA[
<p>
<h3>
<font color="blue">
BRW ICD9X10
<br>
ICD9 &lt;=&gt; ICD10 Translator
</font>
</h3>
</p>

<p>
This app is your tool to easily translate between ICD9 and ICD10 codes.
<br><br>
Translation can go in either direction:
<br> ICD9 =&gt; ICD10 
<br> ICD10 =&gt; ICD9
</p>

<p>
To translate simply tap on the desired code.
</p>
<p>
<font color="blue">Search Tips:</font>
<br>
The default search will search for descriptions that contains the word or phrase you typed in. 
<br>Examples:
<br>Enter <b>knee</b> for a list of ICD codes that contains the word "<b>knee</b>".
<br>Enter <b>open wound</b> for a list of ICD codes that contains the phrase "<b>open wound</b>".
<br><br>
More advanced searching can be performed with the use of the "&amp;" and "|" symbols.
<br>Examples:
<br>Enter <b>knee &amp; ankle</b> for a list of ICD codes that contains the word "<b>knee</b>" and the word "<b>ankle</b>".
<br>Enter <b>knee | ankle</b> for a list of ICD codes that contains one or both of the words "<b>knee</b>" and "<b>ankle</b>".
<br><br>
To search for specific ICD codes, use the "#" symbol. This will search for ICD code that begin the with value you entered.
<br>Example:
<br>Enter <b>#015</b> for a list of ICD codes begin with "<b>015</b>".
<br><br>
To return to browsing all items select <b>Reset Search</b> from the menu.
</p>

<p>
<font color="blue">Managing Folders:</font>
<br>
Customizable folders can be created to hold the ICD codes you select.
<br>Folders can be created for both ICD9 and ICD10 codes.
<br>Select the <b>Manage Folders</b> option from the menu to perform the following functions:
<br> - Add new folders
<br> - Delete folders (long click a single item)
<br> - Rename folders (long click a single item)
</p>

<p>
<font color="blue">Folder View</font>
<br>
When <b>Folder View</b> is enabled ICD codes will be displayed from the <b>Current Folder</b>.
</p>

<p>
<font color="blue">The Current Folder</font>
<br>
When viewing search results, items will always be added to or removed from the <b>Current Folder</b>.  
<br>Use the <b>Set Current Folder</b> menu option to set the <b>Current Folder</b>.
</p>

<p>
<font color="blue">Adding to the Current Folder:</font>
<br>
When viewing search results, items can be added in one of two ways:
<br> - Long click a single item 
<br> - Use the menu to store all items related to your search
</p>
<p>
<font color="blue">Removing from the Current Folder:</font>
<br>
When viewing a folder, items can be removed in one of two ways:
<br> - Long click a single item 
<br> - Use the menu to remove all items related to your search

</p>
      ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
